<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>resources on Webwork.tools</title>
    <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/tags/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in resources on Webwork.tools</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>⧉ Infominer ⧉ CC0 - Public Domain ⧉ Powered by: themes.gohugo.io/indigo via: gohugoio/hugo ⧉</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infominer.id/web-work/tags/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Starter Kit</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hugo-starter-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hugo-starter-kit/</guid>
      <description>All this started a few months ago when I began creating an awesome list on github, then got into publishing via GitHub Pages.
 GitHub Pages Starter Pack GitHub Pages Extended Resources Static Site Generators (just a start) Migrating From Jekyll HPSTR theme to Hugo HPSTR theme Command Line - Git - SSH - BASH  Official Resources  discourse.gohugo.io - Hugo Forum  The language HUGO is built with</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for the Command Line, Git, SSH, and BASH.</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/command-line-git-ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/command-line-git-ssh/</guid>
      <description>I use Ubuntu Linux, so all of my info comes from that perspective. That said, most of it translates pretty simply, and much (most?) of this information is platform independent.
 Learn Enough Command Line to Be Dangerous - Introduction to the Unix command line. Mac to Windows Command Line Mappings reusable materials for bash/git/python bootcamps  Git  The entire Pro Git book -written by Scott Chacon and Ben Straub Learn Enough Git to Be Dangerous Atlassian -Getting Git Right guides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Markup languages that get transformed into a website.</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-html-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-html-css/</guid>
      <description>The_web_standardsmodel-_HTML_CSS_and_JavaScript  Markdown  Mastering Markdown Markdown Cheet-Sheet  TOML - YAML - JSON Just this for now, will get deeper with structured data, later on.
 https://github.com/toml-lang/toml http://yaml.org/ https://www.json.org/  HTML  htmldog.com - HTML5 Beginner Tutorials Learn web development - developer.mozilla.org Learn Enough HTML to be Dangerous  Color  HTML Color Chart Paletton Color Hexa Colors Color Tool  Unicode  Miscellaneous-Symbols-and-Pictographs  Meta Tags  The Head - Metadata in HTML https://metatags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infominer&#39;s Forked Repositores</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/forked-repositories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/forked-repositories/</guid>
      <description>An organized list of my forked repositories.
Now that I have both forked and starred
WebPub  artemsheludko/galada - Galada is an easy and simple blog theme for Jekyll. github/personal-website - A place to track the repositories of infominer. contrafabulists-toolbox/google-sheet-to-github-website - This is a working project for operating a data driven website on Github Pages using Google Sheets as a data source. minicomp/wax - Jekyll for minimal exhibitions with IIIF bee weskerfoot/KettleBlog - A full featured blog in RiotJS poole/lanyon - A content-first, sliding sidebar theme for Jekyll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some tools to make content creation a little easier.
As per usual, this list will grow and become more organized over time.
For now, it&amp;rsquo;s just a copy\paste from the GitHub-Pages Starter Pack.
Basics  Mastering Markdown Markdown Cheet-Sheet  Editors * Visual Studio Code Where I build webpages.
This thing has extensions for all your coding needs&amp;hellip; It is cross-platform, has seamless git integration, and all kind of great features for working with gh-pages repositories (search and replace, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generators</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>Devopedia.org   Well, now i&amp;rsquo;m looking into options besides jekyll, to expand my skills, and try out some themes that aren&amp;rsquo;t available for Jekyll.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, if you are new like me, getting jekyll themes to work is tricky. Many of them are not supported anymore.
What is a Static Site Generator (SSG)? There are some configuration files, layouts and templates, and then there is all your content that your create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indieweb Github Repositories</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-github-repos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-github-repos/</guid>
      <description>github.com/miklb  miklb/webpage-micropub-to-github -forked from voxpelli/webpage-micropub-to-github miklb/jekyll-indieweb  forked.yannick.io/miklb/jekyll-indieweb  miklb/node-micropub-express- forked from voxpelli/node-micropub-express - Provides a Micropub route for Express 4.x miklb/mf2_s- Microformats 2 Version of Underscores Starter Theme with Indieweb Support miklb/hubot-github-issue-lookup -forked from SimplyBuilt/hubot-github-issue-lookup  miklb - WordPress  miklb/wordpress-indieweb-press-this- from indieweb/wordpress-indieweb-press-this.  some IndieWeb magic for WordPress&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;press this&amp;rdquo; bookmarklet.  miklb/wordpress-indieweb- Microformats 2 Version of Underscores Starter Theme with Indieweb Support  github.com/indieweb 101  indieweb/indieweb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indieweb Resources</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-resources/</guid>
      <description>micro.blog/infominer
I was using miklb/jekyll-indieweb, but ran into some bugs and found that a new release is coming soon:

This is indigo, an Indieweb prepared Hugo theme, that I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing about more soon, and figuring out how to make use of all its awesome indieweb integrations.
I cover most anything you&amp;rsquo;d need to get started with GitHub Pages in:
 infominer.id/web-work/github-pages-starter-pack  Taking Back Your Content InfoMine ⧉  https://aaronparecki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using PGP and Cryptocurrency Keysignatures</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/practical-public-key-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/practical-public-key-crypto/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;Public key encryption: supporting secure crypto-currency transactions with strangers online since 1991!!&amp;quot;  I created this resource while researching the following article:
 freelanceforcoins.com/Business with Crypto 101—Escrow and Key Signatures -infominer &amp;gt;This article will explain what is escrow, how to find an escrow agent, and using key signatures to verify who you are communicating with — including the use of Bitcoin and Ethereum signatures to prove (and verify) ownership of a particular address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100&#39;s of Mostly Free SEO Tools</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</guid>
      <description>Google and Company  Google Analytics - duh - free tools to track and analyze website data. Google Webmaster - Tools Suite, Diagnostic Google Search Console - what you&amp;rsquo;re already ranking for, straight from google. Google PageSpeed Insights Google&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Friendly Test Google Sitemap Generators Bing Webmaster Tools - Similar to Google&amp;rsquo;s Webmaster Tools. YouTube Analytics - must-have for YouTube video publishers. A Must-Have Guide for Decoding the Google Rankings  For adding ^^^ this link to my page (It seems like a decent guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Pages-Starter Pack</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-starter-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-starter-pack/</guid>
      <description>Github makes it easy to get started, with the click of a button, you can have a web-page live, requiring only markdown skills (that anyone can learn on the go).
Each feature you want to enable requires a little more learning, and GitHub Pages is set up so that if you decide to, you can gradually progress from content creator to web-developer.
If you don’t want to think about web-development, and simply want your markdown files to look beautiful once published, github pages can help you do that too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Pages-Extended Resources</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-extended-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-extended-resources/</guid>
      <description>Continued from Github Pages Starter Pack.  Related Resources  Learn HTML CSS and Associated Markup Languages Content Creation GitHub Pages Extended Resources Static Site Generators Migrating from Jekyll HPSTR to Hugo HPSTR theme Command Line - Git - SSH - BASH  Setup Front Matter  Front Matter YAML front matter in Jekyll YAML tutorial in the context of Jekyll  Layouts Layouts are preconfigured page templates. When I started, it was too much to think about layouts, and I would use &amp;ldquo;single&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;page&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn SEO</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-seo/</guid>
      <description>SEO seems like a valuable subject to know about right?
The problem with SEO is that there&amp;rsquo;s so much to learn, it&amp;rsquo;s a vast domain of knowledge, with many branches that could each take up thier own websites of related information.
SEO is always changing, and a lot of incorrect or outdated information is republished.
What I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do is break it down into it&amp;rsquo;s various components.
The fundamental building blocks of SEO are:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>