<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources on Webwork.tools: Independent Web-Work and Skyscraper Publishing.</title>
    <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/tags/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resources on Webwork.tools: Independent Web-Work and Skyscraper Publishing.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infominer.id/web-work/tags/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Infominer&#39;s Forked Repositores</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/forked-repositories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/forked-repositories/</guid>
      <description>An organized list of my forked repositories.
Now that I have both forked and starred
WebPub  artemsheludko/galada &amp;gt; Galada is an easy and simple blog theme for Jekyll. github/personal-website &amp;gt; A place to track the repositories of infominer. contrafabulists-toolbox/google-sheet-to-github-website &amp;gt; This is a working project for operating a data driven website on Github Pages using Google Sheets as a data source. &amp;gt; * minicomp/wax &amp;gt; Jekyll for minimal exhibitions with IIIF bee weskerfoot/KettleBlog &amp;gt; A full featured blog in RiotJS poole/lanyon &amp;gt; A content-first, sliding sidebar theme for Jekyll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some tools to make content creation a little easier.
As per usual, this list will grow and become more organized over time.
For now, it&amp;rsquo;s just a copy\paste from the GitHub-Pages Starter Pack.
Basics  Mastering Markdown Markdown Cheet-Sheet  Editors  Visual Studio Code Where I build webpages. ]  This thing has extensions for all your coding needs&amp;hellip; It is cross-platform, has seamless git integration, and all kind of great features for working with gh-pages repositories (search and replace, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generators</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>You may have noticed that the GitHub Pages Starter Pack is getting a bit crowded.
Well, now i&amp;rsquo;m looking into options besides jekyll, to expand my skills, and try out some themes that aren&amp;rsquo;t available for Jekyll.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, if you are new like me, getting jekyll themes to work is tricky. Many of them are not supported anymore.
What is a Static Site Generator (SSG)? There are some configuration files, layouts and templates, and then there is all your content that your create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using PGP and Cryptocurrency Keysignatures</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/practical-public-key-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/practical-public-key-crypto/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;Prove you are who you say you are, with public key encryption: supporting secure crypto-currency transactions with strangers online since 1991!!&amp;quot;  I created this resource while researching the following article:
 freelanceforcoins.com/Business with Crypto 101—Escrow and Key Signatures -infominer &amp;gt;This article will explain what is escrow, how to find an escrow agent, and using key signatures to verify who you are communicating with — including the use of Bitcoin and Ethereum signatures to prove (and verify) ownership of a particular address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100&#39;s of Mostly Free SEO Tools</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</guid>
      <description>Google and Company  Google Analytics - duh - free tools to track and analyze website data. Google Webmaster - Tools Suite, Diagnostic Google Search Console - what you&amp;rsquo;re already ranking for, straight from google. Google PageSpeed Insights Google&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Friendly Test Google Sitemap Generators Bing Webmaster Tools - Similar to Google&amp;rsquo;s Webmaster Tools. YouTube Analytics - must-have for YouTube video publishers. A Must-Have Guide for Decoding the Google Rankings  For adding ^^^ this link to my page (It seems like a decent guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Pages-Extended Resources</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-extended-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-extended-resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Pages-Starter Pack</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-starter-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-starter-pack/</guid>
      <description>Github makes it easy to get started, with the click of a button, you can have a web-page live, requiring only markdown skills (that anyone can learn on the go).
Each feature you want to enable requires a little more learning, and GitHub Pages is set up so that if you decide to, you can gradually progress from content creator to web-developer.
If you don’t want to think about web-development, and simply want your markdown files to look beautiful once published, github pages can help you do that too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn SEO</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-seo/</guid>
      <description>SEO seems like a valuable subject to know about right?
The problem with SEO is that there&amp;rsquo;s so much to learn, it&amp;rsquo;s a vast domain of knowledge, with many branches that could each take up thier own websites of related information.
SEO is always changing, and a lot of incorrect or outdated information is republished.
What I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do is break it down into it&amp;rsquo;s various components.
The fundamental building blocks of SEO are:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>