<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Webwork.tools</title>
    <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Webwork.tools</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>⧉ Infominer ⧉ CC0 - Public Domain ⧉ Powered by: themes.gohugo.io/indigo via: gohugoio/hugo ⧉</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Starter Pack</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hugo-starter-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hugo-starter-pack/</guid>
      <description>All this started a few months ago when I began creating an awesome list on github, then got into publishing via GitHub Pages.
 GitHub Pages Starter Pack GitHub Pages Extended Resources Static Site Generators (just a start) Migrating From Jekyll HPSTR theme to Hugo HPSTR theme Command Line - Git - SSH - BASH  Official Resources  discourse.gohugo.io - Hugo Forum Recommended Reading Reference *** Ton of good stuff in here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for learning HTML, Meta tags, CSS, Kramdown, Katex.</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-html-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-html-css/</guid>
      <description>  htmldog.com - HTML5 and CSS Beginner Tutorials The_web_standardsmodel-_HTML_CSS_and_JavaScript Learn web development - developer.mozilla.org rtable  Color Charts  https://htmlcolorcodes.com/color-chart/  Unicode  unicode-table.com/#miscellaneous-symbols-and-pictographs  Katex  katex Viewport and Media Queries  Meta Tags  The Head - Metadata in HTML https://metatags.io https://www.heymeta.com/  Kramdown  kramdown.gettalong.org Kramdown - Syntax  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for the Command Line, Git, SSH, and BASH.</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/command-line-git-ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/command-line-git-ssh/</guid>
      <description>I use Ubuntu Linux, so all of my info comes from that perspective. That said, most of it translates pretty simply, and much (most?) of this information is platform independent.
 Learn Enough Command Line to Be Dangerous - Introduction to the Unix command line. Mac to Windows Command Line Mappings reusable materials for bash/git/python bootcamps  Git  The entire Pro Git book -written by Scott Chacon and Ben Straub Learn Enough Git to Be Dangerous Atlassian -Getting Git Right guides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FreeNode IRC #indieweb-dev on IIW RWoT and DID&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-dev-on-did/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-dev-on-did/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m hoping for is that folk in the DID community will consider integrating with IndieAuth. This would enable easy adoption for website owners, and make the logical connection between DID and IndieAuth.
Contents  Links  In-Chat Links Peer to Peer DIDs IndieAuth  #indieweb-dev on RWoT-DIDs 2019-03-02 #indieweb-dev on IIW 2018-08-19  Links  indieweb.org/discuss#Join_Discussions Matrix bridge to #dev channnel chat (via riot.im) #indieweb-dev on DIDs 2019-03-02-chat log #indieweb-dev on IIW 2018-08-19-chat log  Related  The Decentralized Identifier (DID) in the DNS  In-chat Links  https://docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indigo Authors - Indiweb Features</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indigo-authors-indieweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indigo-authors-indieweb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;notes-from-the-editor&#34;&gt;Notes from the Editor&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m noticing that the repository hasn&amp;rsquo;t been recently updated by it&amp;rsquo;s owner, however, I can find some helpful contributions from the community:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/AngeloStavrow/indigo/pulls&#34;&gt;https://github.com/AngeloStavrow/indigo/pulls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*note, I changed the date so it would bump to the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;indigo-authors&#34;&gt;Indigo Authors&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom of every page in the theme can optionally show a short biography of the site author, including a profile picture, email link, and location.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll HPSTR-Theme Blog Index Demo</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hpstr-theme-full-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hpstr-theme-full-page/</guid>
      <description> Since I changed the theme too quickly for anyone to really see what it looked like, I&amp;rsquo;ve been saving images of how it used to look.
The whole point was not to just have the same theme, but to be able to try out many Hugo themes&amp;hellip;
Though I really did like the HPSTR theme, I might switch back to the jekyll version even :)
Webwork.tools Jekyll HPSTR Index-Full </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from Jekyll HPSTR to Hugo.</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/migrate-jekyll-hpstr-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/migrate-jekyll-hpstr-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to learn Hugo a few different ways, and finally found one that works for me, and I hope will work well for anyone.
This guide and the accompanying repository should help anyone switching from either Jekyll to Hugo, or Hugo to Jekyll.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got two branches of the same exact website except one is run by Jekyll and one is run by Hugo!!
That&amp;rsquo;s pretty neat, if you ask me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Test Branch and Merging back the Changes</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/branches-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/branches-git/</guid>
      <description>I made a test branch for the swapping jekyll for hugo article, and then merged the changes back to master, once I had it running.
Checkout test branch Use the command git checkout -b will allow you to create a local branch for testing.
I will call my new branch test-hugo so the command will be like so:
git checkout -b test-hugo
Some git basics for newbs like me  Git Branching and Merging  Git keeps track of all your files, but not just the files, but everything in the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infominer&#39;s Forked Repositores</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/forked-repositories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/forked-repositories/</guid>
      <description>An organized list of my forked repositories.
Now that I have both forked and starred
WebPub  artemsheludko/galada - Galada is an easy and simple blog theme for Jekyll. github/personal-website - A place to track the repositories of infominer. contrafabulists-toolbox/google-sheet-to-github-website - This is a working project for operating a data driven website on Github Pages using Google Sheets as a data source. minicomp/wax - Jekyll for minimal exhibitions with IIIF bee weskerfoot/KettleBlog - A full featured blog in RiotJS poole/lanyon - A content-first, sliding sidebar theme for Jekyll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some tools to make content creation a little easier.
As per usual, this list will grow and become more organized over time.
For now, it&amp;rsquo;s just a copy\paste from the GitHub-Pages Starter Pack.
Basics  Mastering Markdown Markdown Cheet-Sheet  Editors * Visual Studio Code Where I build webpages.
This thing has extensions for all your coding needs&amp;hellip; It is cross-platform, has seamless git integration, and all kind of great features for working with gh-pages repositories (search and replace, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infominer&#39;s GitHub Portfolio and HowTo</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/make-a-github-portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/make-a-github-portfolio/</guid>
      <description>I learned of this cool project from @bmann. I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting a simple way to make a page like this for a while!
It&amp;rsquo;s really nice to have a place to keep track, because I&amp;rsquo;m always forgetting how many I even manage!
It might seem intimidating to hear, &amp;ldquo;Just Fork It!&amp;rdquo;
However, you&amp;rsquo;ll see that it&amp;rsquo;s not much more complex than that.
Step 1 Fork this repository:
 github/personal-website  Step 2 Go to settings and select publish from master branch:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infominer&#39;s Starred GitHub Repositories</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-stars/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s all my starred Github Repositories. Ill star a lot more and continue refining this list as time goes on.
I used this:
 kirtan403.github.io/bookmark-github-stars/  and then found this app that makes them even prettier and has an option to push the data to json. (I&amp;rsquo;ll try this next time)
 export-github-stars.netlify.com/  Infominer33&amp;rsquo;s Starred GitHub Repositories  avidLearnerInProgress/python-automation-scripts chaconnewu/awesome-augmented mnyrop/swc-materials mnyrop/pagemaster mozilla/sops jens-maus/yam Jugendhackt/HowToPGP vitalysim/Awesome-Hacking-Resources Hack-with-Github/Awesome-Hacking  GH-Pages  jekyll-toc weskerfoot/artwork weskerfoot/Gitblog weskerfoot/KettleBlog sindresorhus/amas bmann/webpage-webmentions shichao-an/twitter-photos DeeJayhX/HTMLArticleElementStripper unlicense/unlicense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign Up and Get Started using Google Adwords Keyword Planner</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/keyword-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/keyword-planning/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is just a &amp;ldquo;stub&amp;rdquo;, and doesn&amp;rsquo;t go fully into the details of keyword research. I have written an article on the subject, and begun some study of Keyword Research and SEO, although I&amp;rsquo;m not by any means an expert.
I made this, because it was a little confusing for me when I first tried to use it, and I wanted to be sure that eveyone in my organization had a fundamental understanding of keyword research, so they could assist in coming up with seed-keywords, and understand the building blocks of keyword-research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generators</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>Devopedia.org   Well, now i&amp;rsquo;m looking into options besides jekyll, to expand my skills, and try out some themes that aren&amp;rsquo;t available for Jekyll.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, if you are new like me, getting jekyll themes to work is tricky. Many of them are not supported anymore.
What is a Static Site Generator (SSG)? There are some configuration files, layouts and templates, and then there is all your content that your create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Publishing</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/open-source-publishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/open-source-publishing/</guid>
      <description>Shows what can be done in a short period of time. I didn&amp;rsquo;t start building any of this till the beginning of this year.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that it&amp;rsquo;s a ton of work to do what I do, but you could use this concept for just one topic instead of 100 and build a valuable resource in a few days!
I will publish monthly stats, though it won&amp;rsquo;t always be the same, and if you have any requests, pop up in the issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indieweb Github Repositories</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-github-repos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-github-repos/</guid>
      <description>github.com/miklb  miklb/webpage-micropub-to-github -forked from voxpelli/webpage-micropub-to-github miklb/jekyll-indieweb  forked.yannick.io/miklb/jekyll-indieweb  miklb/node-micropub-express- forked from voxpelli/node-micropub-express - Provides a Micropub route for Express 4.x miklb/mf2_s- Microformats 2 Version of Underscores Starter Theme with Indieweb Support miklb/hubot-github-issue-lookup -forked from SimplyBuilt/hubot-github-issue-lookup  miklb - WordPress  miklb/wordpress-indieweb-press-this- from indieweb/wordpress-indieweb-press-this.  some IndieWeb magic for WordPress&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;press this&amp;rdquo; bookmarklet.  miklb/wordpress-indieweb- Microformats 2 Version of Underscores Starter Theme with Indieweb Support  github.com/indieweb 101  indieweb/indieweb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indieweb Resources</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-resources/</guid>
      <description>micro.blog/infominer
I was using miklb/jekyll-indieweb, but ran into some bugs and found that a new release is coming soon:

This is indigo, an Indieweb prepared Hugo theme, that I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing about more soon, and figuring out how to make use of all its awesome indieweb integrations.
I cover most anything you&amp;rsquo;d need to get started with GitHub Pages in:
 infominer.id/web-work/github-pages-starter-pack  Taking Back Your Content InfoMine ⧉  https://aaronparecki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using PGP and Cryptocurrency Keysignatures</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/practical-public-key-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/practical-public-key-crypto/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;Public key encryption: supporting secure crypto-currency transactions with strangers online since 1991!!&amp;quot;  I created this resource while researching the following article:
 freelanceforcoins.com/Business with Crypto 101—Escrow and Key Signatures -infominer &amp;gt;This article will explain what is escrow, how to find an escrow agent, and using key signatures to verify who you are communicating with — including the use of Bitcoin and Ethereum signatures to prove (and verify) ownership of a particular address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100&#39;s of Mostly Free SEO Tools</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</guid>
      <description>Google and Company  Google Analytics - duh - free tools to track and analyze website data. Google Webmaster - Tools Suite, Diagnostic Google Search Console - what you&amp;rsquo;re already ranking for, straight from google. Google PageSpeed Insights Google&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Friendly Test Google Sitemap Generators Bing Webmaster Tools - Similar to Google&amp;rsquo;s Webmaster Tools. YouTube Analytics - must-have for YouTube video publishers. A Must-Have Guide for Decoding the Google Rankings  For adding ^^^ this link to my page (It seems like a decent guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Pages-Starter Pack</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-starter-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-starter-pack/</guid>
      <description>Github makes it easy to get started, with the click of a button, you can have a web-page live, requiring only markdown skills (that anyone can learn on the go).
Each feature you want to enable requires a little more learning, and GitHub Pages is set up so that if you decide to, you can gradually progress from content creator to web-developer.
If you don’t want to think about web-development, and simply want your markdown files to look beautiful once published, github pages can help you do that too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Pages-Extended Resources</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-extended-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-extended-resources/</guid>
      <description>Continued from Github Pages Starter Pack.  Setup Front Matter  Front Matter YAML front matter in Jekyll YAML tutorial in the context of Jekyll  Layouts Layouts are preconfigured page templates. When I started, it was too much to think about layouts, and I would use &amp;ldquo;single&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;page&amp;rdquo;. Now that I am using blog posts.. (because they populate your RSS feed, and increases their portability) I&amp;rsquo;m also using the Home layout:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn SEO</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-seo/</guid>
      <description>SEO seems like a valuable subject to know about right?
The problem with SEO is that there&amp;rsquo;s so much to learn, it&amp;rsquo;s a vast domain of knowledge, with many branches that could each take up thier own websites of related information.
SEO is always changing, and a lot of incorrect or outdated information is republished.
What I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do is break it down into it&amp;rsquo;s various components.
The fundamental building blocks of SEO are:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>