<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Webwork.tools</title>
    <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Webwork.tools</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>⧉ Infominer ⧉ CC0 - Public Domain ⧉ Powered by: themes.gohugo.io/indigo via: gohugoio/hugo ⧉</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Starter Kit</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hugo-starter-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hugo-starter-kit/</guid>
      <description>Interview with Bjørn Erik Pedersen, Hugo lead developer  Official Resources  Quickstart GoHugo Configure - all the cool config.toml settings you never knew! Documentation Forum https://gohugo.io/tools/starter-kits/ Golang - the language HUGO is built with  Golang Templates   Publishing Websites Via Hugo  budparr/awesome-hugo Make A Hugo Blog from Scratch comprehensive-hugo-tutorial-for-beginners Migrating from Jekyll to Hugo &amp;lt;&amp;ndash;good thread https://blog.carlmjohnson.net/post/2017/hugo-asset-pipeline/  Tutorials  https://zwbetz.com/tags/hugo/ https://willschenk.com/tags/hugo/ https://regisphilibert.com/tags/hugo/ Hugo Static Site Tutorials https://discourse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for the Command Line, Git, SSH, and BASH.</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/command-line-git-ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/command-line-git-ssh/</guid>
      <description>I use Ubuntu Linux, so all of my info comes from that perspective. That said, most of it translates pretty simply, and much (most?) of this information is platform independent.
 Learn Enough Command Line to Be Dangerous - Introduction to the Unix command line. Mac to Windows Command Line Mappings reusable materials for bash/git/python bootcamps  Git  The entire Pro Git book -written by Scott Chacon and Ben Straub Learn Enough Git to Be Dangerous Atlassian -Getting Git Right guides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Markup languages that get transformed into a website.</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-html-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-html-css/</guid>
      <description>Trying to keep track of the various languages that our SSGs transform into proper HTML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FreeNode IRC #indieweb-dev on IIW RWoT and DID&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-dev-on-did/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-dev-on-did/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m hoping for is that folk in the DID community will consider integrating with IndieAuth. This would enable easy adoption for website owners, and make the logical connection between DID and IndieAuth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indigo Authors - Indiweb Features</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indigo-authors-indieweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indigo-authors-indieweb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;notes-from-the-editor&#34;&gt;Notes from the Editor&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m noticing that the repository hasn&amp;rsquo;t been recently updated by it&amp;rsquo;s owner, however, I can find some helpful contributions from the community:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/AngeloStavrow/indigo/pulls&#34;&gt;https://github.com/AngeloStavrow/indigo/pulls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*note, I changed the date so it would bump to the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;indigo-authors&#34;&gt;Indigo Authors&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom of every page in the theme can optionally show a short biography of the site author, including a profile picture, email link, and location.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll HPSTR-Theme Blog Index Demo</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hpstr-theme-full-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/hpstr-theme-full-page/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to learn Hugo a few different ways, and finally found one that works for me, and I hope will work well for anyone.
This guide and the accompanying repository should help anyone switching from either Jekyll to Hugo, &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; Hugo to Jekyll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from Jekyll HPSTR to Hugo.</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/migrate-jekyll-hpstr-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/migrate-jekyll-hpstr-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to learn Hugo a few different ways, and finally found one that works for me, and I hope will work well for anyone.
This guide and the accompanying repository should help anyone switching from either Jekyll to Hugo, &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; Hugo to Jekyll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Test Branch and Merging back the Changes</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/branches-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/branches-git/</guid>
      <description>I made a test branch for the swapping jekyll for hugo article, and then merged the changes back to master, once I had it running.
Use the command &lt;code&gt;git checkout -b&lt;/code&gt; will allow you to create a local branch for testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infominer&#39;s Forked Repositores</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/forked-repositories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/forked-repositories/</guid>
      <description>An organized list of my forked repositories.
Now that I have both forked and starred
WebPub  artemsheludko/galada - Galada is an easy and simple blog theme for Jekyll. github/personal-website - A place to track the repositories of infominer. contrafabulists-toolbox/google-sheet-to-github-website - This is a working project for operating a data driven website on Github Pages using Google Sheets as a data source. minicomp/wax - Jekyll for minimal exhibitions with IIIF bee weskerfoot/KettleBlog - A full featured blog in RiotJS poole/lanyon - A content-first, sliding sidebar theme for Jekyll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some tools to make content creation a little easier. As per usual, this list will grow and become more organized over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infominer&#39;s GitHub Portfolio and HowTo</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/make-a-github-portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/make-a-github-portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Now there is a simple way to create a GitHub style portfolio for your github repositories!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infominer&#39;s Starred GitHub Repositories</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-stars/</guid>
      <description>A list of my starred Github Repositories. Ill star a lot more, now that I have a convenient way to organize them, and continue refining this list as time goes on. (primarily for my own convenience)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign Up and Get Started using Google Adwords Keyword Planner</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/keyword-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/keyword-planning/</guid>
      <description>A basic guide to signing up to AdWords Keyword Planner for the first time. Many SEO guides reference this tool, and it can be a little confusing to get started, and that&amp;rsquo;s why I created this short howto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generators</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>There are some configuration files, layouts and templates, and all of the content you create. So.. the trick is to find something that runs nicely on your system and that you can figure out how to operate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Publishing</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/open-source-publishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/open-source-publishing/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll be regularly posting updates from analytics and Google search console, to share how it isn&amp;rsquo;t so impossible to rise through the rankings if you create useful content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indieweb Github Repositories</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-github-repos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-github-repos/</guid>
      <description>github.com/miklb  miklb/webpage-micropub-to-github -forked from voxpelli/webpage-micropub-to-github miklb/jekyll-indieweb  forked.yannick.io/miklb/jekyll-indieweb  miklb/node-micropub-express- forked from voxpelli/node-micropub-express - Provides a Micropub route for Express 4.x miklb/mf2_s- Microformats 2 Version of Underscores Starter Theme with Indieweb Support miklb/hubot-github-issue-lookup -forked from SimplyBuilt/hubot-github-issue-lookup  miklb - WordPress  miklb/wordpress-indieweb-press-this- from indieweb/wordpress-indieweb-press-this.  some IndieWeb magic for WordPress&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;press this&amp;rdquo; bookmarklet.  miklb/wordpress-indieweb- Microformats 2 Version of Underscores Starter Theme with Indieweb Support  github.com/indieweb 101  indieweb/indieweb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indieweb Resources</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/indieweb-resources/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;When you post something on the web, it should belong to you, not a corporation. Too many companies have gone out of business and lost all of their users’ data. By joining the IndieWeb, your content stays yours and in your control.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using PGP and Cryptocurrency Keysignatures</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/practical-public-key-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/practical-public-key-crypto/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s personal. It&amp;rsquo;s private. And it&amp;rsquo;s no one&amp;rsquo;s business but yours. You may be planning a political campaign, discussing your taxes, or having a secret romance. Or you may be communicating with a political dissident in a repressive country. Whatever it is, you don&amp;rsquo;t want your private electronic mail (email) or confidential documents read by anyone else. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with asserting your privacy. Privacy is as apple-pie as the Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100&#39;s of Mostly Free SEO Tools</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</guid>
      <description>All your SEO tools are belong to us! No, really! From the official tools of Google and co, limited trial power tools, analytics, link building, content creation and much more! All organized by category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Pages-Starter Pack</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-starter-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-starter-pack/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Github makes it easy to get started, with the click of a button, you can have a web-page live, requiring only markdown skills (that anyone can learn on the go).
Each feature you want to enable requires a little more learning, and  GitHub Pages is set up so that if you decide to, you can gradually progress from content creator to web-developer.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Pages-Extended Resources</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-extended-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/github-pages-extended-resources/</guid>
      <description>Continued from Github Pages Starter Pack.  Related Resources  Learn HTML CSS and Associated Markup Languages Content Creation GitHub Pages Extended Resources Static Site Generators Migrating from Jekyll HPSTR to Hugo HPSTR theme Command Line - Git - SSH - BASH  Setup Front Matter  Front Matter YAML front matter in Jekyll YAML tutorial in the context of Jekyll  Layouts Layouts are preconfigured page templates. When I started, it was too much to think about layouts, and I would use &amp;ldquo;single&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;page&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn SEO</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/learn-seo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The fundamental building blocks of SEO are Keyword Research, Content, Internal linking, Site Structure, and a Multitude of Technical Optimizations.
Most of those optimizations revolve around gradually making every individual piece of code on your site more machine readable, so that it communicates essential bits of information to a variety of connecting sites\services that make it stand out from the crowd.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>