<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on Webwork.tools: Independent Web-Work and Skyscraper Publishing.</title>
    <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/tags/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on Webwork.tools: Independent Web-Work and Skyscraper Publishing.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infominer.id/web-work/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some tools to make content creation a little easier.
As per usual, this list will grow and become more organized over time.
For now, it&amp;rsquo;s just a copy\paste from the GitHub-Pages Starter Pack.
Basics  Mastering Markdown Markdown Cheet-Sheet  Editors  Visual Studio Code Where I build webpages. ]  This thing has extensions for all your coding needs&amp;hellip; It is cross-platform, has seamless git integration, and all kind of great features for working with gh-pages repositories (search and replace, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generators</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>You may have noticed that the GitHub Pages Starter Pack is getting a bit crowded.
Well, now i&amp;rsquo;m looking into options besides jekyll, to expand my skills, and try out some themes that aren&amp;rsquo;t available for Jekyll.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, if you are new like me, getting jekyll themes to work is tricky. Many of them are not supported anymore.
What is a Static Site Generator (SSG)? There are some configuration files, layouts and templates, and then there is all your content that your create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100&#39;s of Mostly Free SEO Tools</title>
      <link>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infominer.id/web-work/posts/seo-tools/</guid>
      <description>Google and Company  Google Analytics - duh - free tools to track and analyze website data. Google Webmaster - Tools Suite, Diagnostic Google Search Console - what you&amp;rsquo;re already ranking for, straight from google. Google PageSpeed Insights Google&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Friendly Test Google Sitemap Generators Bing Webmaster Tools - Similar to Google&amp;rsquo;s Webmaster Tools. YouTube Analytics - must-have for YouTube video publishers. A Must-Have Guide for Decoding the Google Rankings  For adding ^^^ this link to my page (It seems like a decent guide.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>